Vaishnavi Gulwelkar

Frontend/UI Developer

About Me

A UI Developer with 2.6 years of hands-on experience on web designing and development and a Google certified User Experience Designer. Having hands-on experience on technologies like HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap4, JavaScript, jQuery, Angular 12 and WordPress.

My Contact



📉 vaishnavigulwelkar922@gmail.com



+91 9673085934



in https://www.linkedin.com/in/va ishnavi-qulwelkar/

Skills

- HTML5
- CSS3
- JavaScript
- jQuery
- Bootstrap4
- Angular Js
- Angular 12
- WordPress

Soft Skill

- Good Learner
- Communication
- Time Management

Education Background

• M.Sc. Computer Science 2020-2022

I have completed master's of computer science from Dr. Babasaheb Ambedkar Marathwada University of Aurangabad.

• B.Sc. 2017 - 2020

I have completed my graduation from Dr. Babasaheb Ambedkar Marathwada University of Aurangabad.

Professional Experience

Salt Technologies | Frontend Developer

7th Dec 2022 - Till Date

Key responsibilities:

 Working on technologies like HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap4, JavaScript, jQuery, WordPress.

Capgemini | Senior Analyst

30th Sep 2021 - 6th Dec 2022

Key responsibilities:

 Worked on technologies like HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap4, Angular 12, JavaScript, jQuery.

Soft-Smart Technology | Jr. Software Developer

10th Jan 2020 - 31st Mar 2021

Key responsibilities:

- Worked on technologies like HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap4, AngularJS, JavaScript, ¡Query.
- · Worked on social media marketing.

Personal Details

Name: Vaishnavi Gulwelkar

Father's Name: Ganpat Gulwelkar

Date Of Birth: 9th Feb 2000

Gender: **Female** Marital Status: **Unmarried**

Nationality: Indian

Languages: English, Hindi, Marathi

Declaration

Hereby I declare that all the above information stated is correct and complete to the best of my belief and knowledge.

Date: 14 Jan 2023 Vaishnavi Gulwelkar